<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Radiofrequency-Diathermy &#8211; Medika Supplies</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/globus/radiofrequency-diathermy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Supply quality products to the medical industries</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 07:45:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>RF Beauty 6000</title>
		<link>/product/rf-beauty-6000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 07:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1212</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Diathermy is a therapy that can produce energy and bring about a sensation of warmth in the treated area. The increase in temperature in the tissues gradually generates the restructuring of collagen superficially and deeply, thus making skin more compact and erasing the marks of time. Heat energy activates fibroblasts, which produce new collagen, thus regenerating tissues (collagenesis). The derma is therefore toned and the skin is smoother.
STRONG POINTS: diathermy can have extraordinary effects on the most widespread skin flaws, with no need to resort to aesthetic surgery or invasive methodologies. Moreover, the first results can be seen very soon after the first applications.
MULTI-FREQUENCY: Rf Beauty 6000 can emit different frequencies (from 400 kHz to 1 MHz). This technology has the outstanding advantage of reaching and working on different body tissues, from wrinkles to deep cellulite. Frequency of emission, is related to the depth of action (higher frequencies work in the surface).
MAIN INDICATIONS:
- face skin laxity
- Neck and cleavage skin laxity
- Abdomen laxity and adiposity
- Tights-gluteus-knees Laxity and adiposity
- Arms Laxity and adiposity
- Cellulite
- Stretch marks
- Scares
- Acne
- And wrinkles]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/6000.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Outputs: 2<br />
Handpieces: capacitive and resistive + resistive bipolar<br />
Emission frequency: 400-470-680 KHz e 1MHz<br />
Emission power:<br />
&#8211; Resistive: 25 Watt<br />
&#8211; Capacitive: 50 Watt<br />
Power supply: mains 220V 50/60 Hz<br />
Size: 17 x 22 x 6 cm; Weight: 900 gr.<br />
Display: color, backlit, touch screen display</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Professional carrying case<br />
1 Rf Beauty 6000 unit<br />
1 counter electrode (plate)<br />
1 resistive handpiece with 3 heads of 30-<br />
50-70 mm Ø<br />
1 capacitive handpiece with 3 heads of<br />
30-50-70 mm Ø<br />
1 bipolar handpiece of 30mm Ø<br />
1 Operating manual<br />
1 Power supply<br />
1 Cream</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rf Beauty Mini</title>
		<link>/product/rf-beauty-mini/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 07:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1214</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GLOBUS Rf Beauty Mini is a radio frequency portable device for beauty applications and against face skin aging.
Globus Rf Beauty Mini, thanks to radio frequency, makes your skin firmer and enhances the synthesis of new collagen and elastin.
At the same time, Globus Rf Beauty Mini, thanks to the thermal effect, improves microcirculation as well as oxygen and nutrient supply to the tissues, which will have a new vitality.
Globus Rf Beauty Mini helps reduce wrinkles as well as rejuvenate your skin and your eye contour.
Globus Rf Beauty Mini is simple and rapid to use and it is supplied with a convenient elegant red carrying case.
PROGRAM LIST
- skin rejuvenation around eyes
- wrinkle reduction
- skin rejuvenation
All the programs have 4 intensity levels.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/mini.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Power: 24 W<br />
Frequency: 1.15+0.1MHz<br />
Power supply: mains 100V ~240V<br />
Size: 15.5 x 5.5 x 2.5 cm<br />
Weight: 0.5 kg<br />
Resistive system</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 carrying case<br />
1 Rf Beauty Mini device<br />
1 operating manual<br />
1 gel bottle</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>RF CLINIC BODY</title>
		<link>/product/rf-clinic-body/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1216</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GLOBUS RF CLINIC BODY es un innovativo aparato PROFESIONAL que genera ondas de radiofrecuencia para aplicaciones estéticas, contra el envejecimiento de la piel ya sea del rostro o de todo el cuerpo.
Globus RF Clinic BODY favorece también la vascularización y la regeneración del tejido cutáneo eliminando las imperfecciones causadas por la exposición a los rayos solares y el envejecimiento de la piel.
APLICACIONES DE LA RADIOFRECUENCIA
Numerosas investigaciones científicas han demostrado que la
RADIOFRECUENCIA estimula la circulación y el metabolismo celular produciendo
- Atenuación de las arrugas y nivelación de la piel
- Recuperación de la elastina cutánea (elastosis y laxitud cutánea)
Gracias a la Tecnología GLOBUS, que permite de controlar todos los parámetros de impulso (frecuencia de estímulo de 470 KHz a 2 MHz, duración y potencia), es posible modular la energía sobre el área a tratar para obtener la máxima eficacia ya sea en las aplicaciones superficiales como en los tratamientos profundos.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/RF-ClinicBody.jpg'></p><p>CARACTERISTICAS TECNICAS<br />
Potencia manípulo: 200 W ( a 50Ω)<br />
Salida: 1<br />
Manípulo: 1RF Clinic 100<br />
Frecuencia de emisión: de 470 KHz a 2<br />
MHz<br />
Alimentación: a red 220V 50/60 Hz o<br />
batería recargable (no en dotación)<br />
Dimensiones: 17 x 22 x 6 cm<br />
Display retroiluminado<br />
Modo de funcionamiento: resistivo<br />
Dispositivo CE</p>
<p>DOTACION<br />
1 valijita<br />
1 unidad Globus RF Clinic BODY<br />
1 manípulo RF Clinic 100<br />
1 manual<br />
1 Gel<br />
1 cargador<br />
ACCESSOIRE EN OPTION<br />
Manípulo Rf Clinic 300 (Ø 30 mm)<br />
Manípulo RF Clinic 500 (Ø 50 mm)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>RF CLINIC Pro</title>
		<link>/product/rf-clinic-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 07:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1219</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[GLOBUS RF CLINIC PRO is an innovative PROFESSIONAL device creating radio frequency waves for beauty applications against the aging of face and body skin and, thanks to the new handpiece, it can also be used for cellulite and firming treatment.
Globus RF Clinic PRO enhances the vascularization and the regeneration of the skin tissue, eliminating the imperfections due to the sun exposure and to the skin aging.
RADIO FREQUENCY APPLICATIONS
Many scientific researches have shown that RADIO
FREQUENCY stimulates circulation and cell metabolism by producing
- wrinkle reduction and skin smoothing
- skin elasticity recovery (elastosis and skin laxity)
Thanks to the GLOBUS Technology, that allows to control all the pulse parameters ( Emission freq. from 470 KHz to 2 MHz, duration and power), it is possible to modify the energy on the treated area in order to obtain the maximum effectiveness both in superficial and deep treatments.
HOW RADIO FREQUENCY WORKS
Radio frequency (RF) produces energy, perceived as heat, stimulating the metabolism of the treated tissues. The RF Radio frequency flow, through the skin, produces an increase in the temperature of the underlying tissues, especially in the supporting structures, elastin and collagen fibers, enhancing their elasticity and firmness.
Heat energy activates the fibroblasts stimulating them to create new collagen with a consequent tissue regeneration (collagenesis). In this way the dermis is more tonic and relaxed.
10 FREE PROGRAMS
 7 FACE programs
 area for face treatments
 13 SKIN programs
 area for body skin treatments
 10 CELLULITE programs
 area for cellulite and adiposity treatment]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/RF-ClinicPro.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Power: 200 W (50 Ω)<br />
Outputs: 1 &#8211; Handpiece: 1 RF Clinic<br />
100 and 1 RF Clinic 500<br />
Emission frequency: from 470 KHz to 2<br />
MHz Power supply: 220V 50/60 Hz<br />
mains or rechargeable battery (not<br />
included)<br />
Size: 17 x 22 x 6 cm<br />
Backlit display<br />
Coupling system: resistive<br />
Device</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 carrying case<br />
1 Globus RF Clinic Pro unit<br />
1 RF Clinic 100 handpiece<br />
1 RF Clinic 500 handpiece<br />
1 Operating manual<br />
1 Gel bottle<br />
ACCESSORIES NOT INCLUDED<br />
1 RF Clinic 300 handpiece (Ø 30 mm)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
