<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Globus &#8211; Medika Supplies</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/globus/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Supply quality products to the medical industries</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 06:42:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>ACTIVA 700</title>
		<link>/product/activa-700/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 02:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[13 Face-Skin G-Pulse © – 60 Beauty – 58 Fitness – 53 Sport
21 Special Sports – 12 Tens – 3 Rehabilitation – 3 Incontinence
12 Microcurrents – 36 “3S” Serial Sequential Stimulation

ADVANCED TECHNOLOGIES IN THE NEW 2013 RANGE
Globus presents an innovative technology intended to revolutionize the electrostimulation application in beauty, sport and medical fields: 3S (Serial Sequential Stimulation) technology.

“3S” SERIAL SEQUENTIAL STIMULATION: The sequential contraction of the different muscular groups produces a deep pressure wave in the musculature involved causing the interstitial fluid drainage and enhancing the return of the venous blood to the heart.

FACE-SKIN TREATMENTS: ACTIVA 700 offers the new innovative and regenerative G-PULSE currents, proposed for Aesthetic and Beauty applications and able to regenerate the collagen production in the tissues.

G-TRODE HEAD: ACTIVA 700 is equipped with a special head that permits, using the G-PULSE programs, to obtain a more effective skin
stimulation.

NEW TRENDY CARRYING CASE: ACTIVA 700 is supplied with a practical modern carrying case in aluminum and eco leather that can be carried in an easy way and that makes you feel always fashionable.

FACE AND BREAST AREA: ACTIVA 700 is equipped with a complete set of programs for face and breast toning

SPECIAL SPORTS: a special program list to stimulate in an effective and specific manner the muscular areas used in the more common sport activities.

MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 10 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.

AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity
regulation.

SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.

RUN TIME FUCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment

PROGRAMMABLE: 10 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 15 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Activa-700.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical, compensated<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Back-lit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive<br />
93/42/CEE-2007/47/CEE</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 carrying case<br />
1 ACTIVA 700 electrostimulator<br />
1 G-Trode head<br />
4 electrostimulation cables and 2<br />
microcurrent cables<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes and 4<br />
self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Gel bottle<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>B-MAT</title>
		<link>/product/b-mat/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 06:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1189</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bed Mat is a true mat made up of 4 interchangeable sections, each containing 4 solenoids.
The Bed Mat has been devised to be placed on a traditional bed mattress, enabling users to perform magnetotherapy treatments during sleep.
Bed Mat takes benefit from magnetic fields to treat the main musculoskeletal disorders such as arthrosis, osteoporosis, arthritis, etc.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Mat.jpg'></p><p>B-Mat is available in three versions:<br />
 B-Mat 200 the mat is made up of two active sections containing 8 solenoids, and of two neutral sections without solenoids. The sections containing solenoids can be shifted to different body parts according to individual needs.<br />
 B-Mat 300 The mat is made up of three active sections containing 12 solenoids, and of one neutral section without solenoids. The sections containing solenoids can be shifted to different body parts according to individual needs.<br />
 B-Mat 400 the mat is made up of four active sections containing 16 solenoids.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CYCLING PRO</title>
		<link>/product/cycling-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The CYCLING PRO electrostimulator is a device dedicated to cyclists who want to feel good and feel healthy during their cycling activity.
The specific programs for cycling are divided into four big macro-areas.

“PAIN-INJURIES” AREA

4 programs to treat the traumas and the recurring ailments in cycling. Specific protocols are included to:
- relieve muscle tension on the cervical area and the shoulders;
- promote recovery after lesions and muscle contractures;
- relieve muscle and joint back pains;
- treat knee inflammations.

“RECOVERY” AREA

6 programs dedicated to relax and loosen the tired muscles. In particular these programs aim to:
- relieve the contracted muscle at the end of the training and/or competition;
- speed recovery between two sessions if you practiced competitions or stage races;
- give relief to the neck and shoulders when they are particularly tense because of the hours spent in the saddle.

“PHYSICAL TRAINING” AREA

34 programs to improve the muscular qualities of the cyclist, taking into account the specific needs of those who practice road cycling or mountain biking.
- increase strength and allow to direct the work of the muscle fibers to the specialty practiced;
- prevent and reduce the risk of joint traumas and muscle injuries;
- allow the cyclist to better withstand long bike rides;
- improve the specific strength and thus the ability of a spurt and sprint, as well as the ability of endurance strength, and necessary for example to tackle climbs;
- provide specific trainings for the upper limbs, especially for those who practice mountain biking and are subjected to continuous vibrations of the handlebars.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Cycling-Pro.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0.3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA for each channel Pulse<br />
amplitude: 40 – 450 μs Waveform: square, twophase,<br />
symmetrical, balanced<br />
Power source: rechargeable battery-powered<br />
Back-illuminated display<br />
Device in II A Class<br />
In compliance with the 93/42/CEE-2007/47/CEE<br />
directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 bag<br />
1 CYCLING PRO stimulator<br />
4 cables for connecting electrodes<br />
2 cables for treatments with MCR and<br />
ionophoresis<br />
4 self-adhesive and square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive and rectangular electrodes<br />
1 battery charger<br />
1 operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DiaCaRe 1000 RT</title>
		<link>/product/diacare-1000-rt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 09:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1121</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Heal your body by using inner energy and natural tissue and muscle self-regeneration mechanisms. This is the main principle of the therapy based on the new revolutionary diathermy technique (also known as TECARTHERAPY).
Diathermy (TECARTHERAPY) works in either capacitive mode or resistive mode. DiaCaRe 1000 RT can work in resistive mode. Therefore, the biological effect will focus on the tissues with higher resistance more effectively (i.e. on the tissues that contain less water).
DiaCaRe 1000 RT can work in resistive mode at a frequency of 470 KHz with a power of 50 W ac.

The portable DiaCaRe 1000 RT comes with an internal rechargeable battery which makes its use possible even without plugging it in. It is very practical for all those emergency situations where there is no electric outlet.

DIATRODE: unique in its category, this accessory permits the use of special electrode pads, directly applied on the part to be treated, maintaining the effectiveness of the therapy with no need for continuous operator assistance. Supplied.

MONOTRODE: this all-in-one handpiece permits to follow traditional application techniques but in a much simplified manner. There is no need to connect the return electrode, which is already contained in the same bipolar handpiece. Supplied.

DUALTRODE: accessory that consists of a monopolar handpiece and a return electrode pad. Not supplied.

INDICATIONS, APPLICATIONS
Particularly indicated for the treatment of: osteoarthritis, bursitis, cervical arthrosis, chondropathy, contractures, contusions, sprains, strains, lesions, luxations, periarthritis, sciatica, ligament traumas, tendinitis.

REHABILITATION: treatment of all acute and chronic osteoarticular and muscular pathologies.

SPORT APPLICATIONS: to reduce and prevent traumas during athletic training, to favor recovery.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/DiaCaRe-1000-RT.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL CHARACTERISTICS<br />
Power: 50 W ac<br />
Outlets: 1<br />
Handpieces: DiaTrode, MonoTrode<br />
Output frequency: 470 KHz<br />
Power supply: mains 220V 50/60 Hz or<br />
rechargeable battery (supplied)<br />
Dimensions: 17 x 22 x 6 cm<br />
Backlit display<br />
Coupling system: resistive<br />
MDD-certified device</p>
<p>INCLUDED<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 Device DiaCare 1000 rt<br />
1 DiaTrode cable<br />
1 MonoTrode handpiece<br />
4 DiaTrode S electrod pads<br />
1 Manual<br />
1 cream can<br />
NOT INCLUDED<br />
DualTrode handpiece</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DiaCare 5000</title>
		<link>/product/diacare-5000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 09:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1117</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Tecar Therapy is a form of endogenous thermotherapy that stimulates the body's natural repair processes, speeding up tissue recovery time during treatment of injuries and diseases of the musculoskeletal system. Diacare 5000 is the portable device of the Globus Tecar Therapy line and it is enriched with new features.

NEW GRAPHIC INTERFACE: to use the color touchscreen display in an intuitive way.

PRESET PROGRAMS: the new Diacare 5000 offers a list of preset programs to treat the most common disorders of the musculoskeletal system.

NEW PROGRAMS: ability to create new programs and save them in an appropriate memory.

AUTOMATIC TREATMENT: it allows the use of carbon electrodes to be fixed to the patient's body. In this way, the operator will have the opportunity to integrate therapy with manual techniques.

MULTI-FREQUENCY: Diacare 5000 can use different working frequencies. The ability to have multiple frequencies allows the operator to intervene in a timely manner on different tissues, even at different depths.

AUTOMATIC FREQUENCY SCANNING: the program allows, within the same treatment, to transport energy in an uniform way, before in the deeper tissues, then in the middle, and finally in the more superficial tissues.

TRANSDERMAL DELIVERY: the program allows to facilitate the absorption of the active principle of a drug or cream.

ATHERMY TREATMENTS: the athermic program, thanks to the pulsed controlled emission, is modulated to create a biostimulation of the tissue without generating heat.

PULSED TREATMENT: ability to use programs with pulsed emission of different ratio (duty cycle). This allows to maintain high the energy transferred to the tissues preserving, at the same time, a good temperature control.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/diacare5000.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Power: 200W ± 10%<br />
Outputs: 2<br />
Handpieces: 2<br />
Treatment modality: capacitive and resistive<br />
Output frequency: 400-470-700-1000 kHz ±10%<br />
Size: 170x220x60 mm<br />
Weight: 1,1 Kg</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Professional carrying case<br />
1 Diacare 5000 device<br />
1 Counter electrode (plate)<br />
1 Monopolar resistive handpiece with 3 heads<br />
of 30-50-70 mm Ø<br />
1 Monopolar capacitive handpiece with 3<br />
heads of 30-50-70 mm Ø<br />
1 Operating manual<br />
1 Power supply unit<br />
1 Cream<br />
1 DVD with treatment videos</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DUO PRO</title>
		<link>/product/duo-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[• 35 PROGRAMS FITNESS, HEALTH AND BEAUTY in the palm of your hand
• BACKLIT DISPLAY
• SOFT TOUCH FINISH: Duo Pro offers a pleasant feeling in your hands. Its coating makes it very soft.
• EASY TO USE
• ABILITY TO CUSTOMIZE TIME IN EACH PROGRAM
• HIGH TECH &#38; DESIGN: Duo Pro is a handheld stimulator with modern and innovative design, compact size, backlit display.
• A FULL COMPLEMENT OF THE BEST PROGRAMS: To provide superior performance with ease of use.
• SPORTS AND PERFORMANCE: 7 essential programs for training and sports performance.
• FITNESS: 20 programs to achieve and maintain a perfect physical shape. The best solution to restore the balance and beauty of your body.
• HEALTH AND WELLBEING: 8 specific applications for the treatment of pain, acute and chronic inflammatory disorders in the musculoskeletal system.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Duo-Pro.jpg'></p><p>SPECIFICATIONS<br />
Channels: 2 independent channels<br />
Frequency: 1 to 120 Hz<br />
Power: 40 mA per channel<br />
Pulse width: 50 to 320 μs<br />
Waveform: square, biphasic, symmetrical<br />
and balanced wave<br />
Power supply: 3 batteries 1,5 V AAA<br />
Device Class II Type BF</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 bag<br />
A stimulator PRO DUO<br />
2 cables for connecting the electrodes<br />
4 Square self-adhesive electrodes<br />
4 Rectangular self-adhesive electrodes<br />
1 Operating Manual<br />
3 AAA Batteries</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DUO TENS</title>
		<link>/product/duo-tens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1133</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[4 Fitness, Beauty, Wellness – 16 Pain –Tens
Globus presents the new Duo Tens electrostimulator with a completely innovated design and performance.
PROGRAMMABLE: Duo Tens has 6 free memories where it is possible to insert the desired parameters and to create your personalized
programs.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.
PAIN: It eliminates the pain with the special pulses of the TENS currents that, stimulating your body in a soft way, enables you to recover your
health, wellness and a renovated life enjoyment.
FITNESS, BEAUTY &#38; WELNESS: body beauty is the expression of a wellness state and a form balance that you have to value and defend from the attacks of time and sedentary life. With Duo Tens you can care for your body, defending its vitality and beauty using the main programs for physical shape.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/DuoTens.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 2 independent<br />
CHANNELS Frequency: 0 –<br />
150 Hz<br />
Power: 100 mA per channel Pulse<br />
amplitude: 50 – 400 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical and compensated wave<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Backlit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS Duo Tens Stimulator<br />
2 Cables for electrode connection<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular<br />
electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ELITE SII</title>
		<link>/product/elite-sii/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[30 Sport - 44 Fitness, Beauty, Wellness – 16 Pain –Tens
6 Prevention – 3 Rehabilitation - 1 Incontinence
Globus presents the new Elite SII electrostimulator with a completely improved design and performance.

PROGRAMMABLE: ELITE SII has 6 free memories where it is possible to insert the desired parameters and to create your personalized programs.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.
PREVENTION: 6 programs to reinforce main articulations and to prevent traumas and injuries.
SPORT: EliteSII is programed to selectively stimulate fast and slow fibers in order to train different muscle qualities
FITNESS, BEAUTY &#38; WELNESS: Thanks to its compactness, lightness and power supply with rechargeable battery, Elite SII is the ideal tool to make an home exercise program to reach and maintain the physical shape.
You can care for your body and defend its vitality and beauty with the electrostimulation beauty treatments.
REHABILITATION &#38; PAIN
REHABILITATION: Muscle stimulation programs are particularly indicated for functional recovery after surgical articulation interventions and after immobilization time
PAIN: It eliminates the pain with the special pulses of the TENS currents that, stimulating your body in a soft way, enables you to recover your health, wellness and a renovated life enjoyment.
INCONTINENCE: one specific program to treat at home this common disorder.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Elite-S2.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 2 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0 –150 Hz<br />
Power: 100 mA p.p. for channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 50 – 400 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic, symmetrical<br />
and compensated wave<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Back-lit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS ELITE SII Stimulator<br />
1 Cables for electrode connection<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>EPILMAX G-LIGHT 500</title>
		<link>/product/epilmax-g-light-500/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 08:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Epilmax G-Light 500 is the model of the well proven line of machines IPL Equipped with the new technology PULSED LIGHT. In addition to the traditional feature of removing undesired hair permanently, includes the very new Anti Age function.

HAIR REMOVAL FUNCTION

Laser epilation consists in the use of the laser energy for a definitive hair reduction . Epilmax G-Light emits a flash of very high intensity light energy that get absorbed by the hair’s melanin pigment, thus causing a fast overheating of the hair follicle. The heat destroys the dermal papilla (hair follicle), responsible of the hair’s growth.

REJUVENATION FUNCTION
“Skin photorejuvenation” means a group of dermatological procedures that use specific high-intensity pulsed light sources (IPL), to generate corrective biological effects in the tissues altered by photoaging (sun damage), chronological ageing (age), and other gained alterations Epilmax G-Light can be easily carried and used in comfortably at home; it permits to reduce hair according to your needs, always and everywhere.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Epilmax-G-Light-500.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Bandwidth 470/1100 nm<br />
Power output: 1,8J/cm (Rejuvenation)<br />
Power output: da 3 a 5 J/cm2 (Epilation)<br />
Lamps duration : 6000 flash (Epilation)<br />
Lamps duration: 20.000 flash<br />
(Rejuvenation)<br />
Unit weight: 1.7 kg<br />
Power supply: rete a 220V.</p>
<p>ACCESSORIES INCLUDED<br />
1 IPL Unit<br />
2 Xenon Lamps<br />
1 Cable adapter<br />
1 User’s manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FIT &#038; BEAUTY</title>
		<link>/product/fit-beauty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[13 G-Pulse Face-Skin © - 65 Beauty – 58 Fitness – 22 Sport –12
Tens-Pain – 3 Rehabilitation – 3 Incontinence – 12 Microcurrents
–
FACE-SKIN TREATMENTS: Fit &#38; Beauty presents the new innovative and regenerative G-PULSE currents, proposed for Aesthetic and
Beauty applications and able to regenerate the collagen production in the tissues.
G-TRODE HANDPIECE Fit &#38; Beauty is equipped with a special handpiece that permits, using the G-PULSE programs, to obtain a more effective skin stimulation.
NEW TRENDY CARRIAGE CASE: Fit &#38; Beauty is supplied with a practical modern carrying case in aluminum and eco leather that can be carried in an easy way and that makes you feel always fashionable.
FACE &#38; BREAST AREAS: Fit &#38; Beauty is equipped with a complete set of programs for face and breast toning
MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 10 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.
PROGRAMMABLE: 10 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity regulation.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button .
RUN TIME FUNCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 15 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/FitBeauty.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz &#8211; Power: 120 mA<br />
per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical, compensated wave<br />
Power supply: mains or battery<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 Fit &amp; Beauty stimulator<br />
1 G-Trode handpiece<br />
4 electrostimulation cables and 2<br />
microcurrent cables<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes and 4<br />
self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Gel bottle<br />
1 power supply<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
