<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Electrotherapy &#8211; Medika Supplies</title>
	<atom:link href="/product-category/globus/electrotherapy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Supply quality products to the medical industries</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:10:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>ACTIVA 700</title>
		<link>/product/activa-700/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 02:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[13 Face-Skin G-Pulse © – 60 Beauty – 58 Fitness – 53 Sport
21 Special Sports – 12 Tens – 3 Rehabilitation – 3 Incontinence
12 Microcurrents – 36 “3S” Serial Sequential Stimulation

ADVANCED TECHNOLOGIES IN THE NEW 2013 RANGE
Globus presents an innovative technology intended to revolutionize the electrostimulation application in beauty, sport and medical fields: 3S (Serial Sequential Stimulation) technology.

“3S” SERIAL SEQUENTIAL STIMULATION: The sequential contraction of the different muscular groups produces a deep pressure wave in the musculature involved causing the interstitial fluid drainage and enhancing the return of the venous blood to the heart.

FACE-SKIN TREATMENTS: ACTIVA 700 offers the new innovative and regenerative G-PULSE currents, proposed for Aesthetic and Beauty applications and able to regenerate the collagen production in the tissues.

G-TRODE HEAD: ACTIVA 700 is equipped with a special head that permits, using the G-PULSE programs, to obtain a more effective skin
stimulation.

NEW TRENDY CARRYING CASE: ACTIVA 700 is supplied with a practical modern carrying case in aluminum and eco leather that can be carried in an easy way and that makes you feel always fashionable.

FACE AND BREAST AREA: ACTIVA 700 is equipped with a complete set of programs for face and breast toning

SPECIAL SPORTS: a special program list to stimulate in an effective and specific manner the muscular areas used in the more common sport activities.

MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 10 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.

AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity
regulation.

SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.

RUN TIME FUCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment

PROGRAMMABLE: 10 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 15 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Activa-700.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical, compensated<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Back-lit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive<br />
93/42/CEE-2007/47/CEE</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 carrying case<br />
1 ACTIVA 700 electrostimulator<br />
1 G-Trode head<br />
4 electrostimulation cables and 2<br />
microcurrent cables<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes and 4<br />
self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Gel bottle<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>CYCLING PRO</title>
		<link>/product/cycling-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1131</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The CYCLING PRO electrostimulator is a device dedicated to cyclists who want to feel good and feel healthy during their cycling activity.
The specific programs for cycling are divided into four big macro-areas.

“PAIN-INJURIES” AREA

4 programs to treat the traumas and the recurring ailments in cycling. Specific protocols are included to:
- relieve muscle tension on the cervical area and the shoulders;
- promote recovery after lesions and muscle contractures;
- relieve muscle and joint back pains;
- treat knee inflammations.

“RECOVERY” AREA

6 programs dedicated to relax and loosen the tired muscles. In particular these programs aim to:
- relieve the contracted muscle at the end of the training and/or competition;
- speed recovery between two sessions if you practiced competitions or stage races;
- give relief to the neck and shoulders when they are particularly tense because of the hours spent in the saddle.

“PHYSICAL TRAINING” AREA

34 programs to improve the muscular qualities of the cyclist, taking into account the specific needs of those who practice road cycling or mountain biking.
- increase strength and allow to direct the work of the muscle fibers to the specialty practiced;
- prevent and reduce the risk of joint traumas and muscle injuries;
- allow the cyclist to better withstand long bike rides;
- improve the specific strength and thus the ability of a spurt and sprint, as well as the ability of endurance strength, and necessary for example to tackle climbs;
- provide specific trainings for the upper limbs, especially for those who practice mountain biking and are subjected to continuous vibrations of the handlebars.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Cycling-Pro.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0.3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA for each channel Pulse<br />
amplitude: 40 – 450 μs Waveform: square, twophase,<br />
symmetrical, balanced<br />
Power source: rechargeable battery-powered<br />
Back-illuminated display<br />
Device in II A Class<br />
In compliance with the 93/42/CEE-2007/47/CEE<br />
directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 bag<br />
1 CYCLING PRO stimulator<br />
4 cables for connecting electrodes<br />
2 cables for treatments with MCR and<br />
ionophoresis<br />
4 self-adhesive and square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive and rectangular electrodes<br />
1 battery charger<br />
1 operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DUO PRO</title>
		<link>/product/duo-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 05:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1170</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[• 35 PROGRAMS FITNESS, HEALTH AND BEAUTY in the palm of your hand
• BACKLIT DISPLAY
• SOFT TOUCH FINISH: Duo Pro offers a pleasant feeling in your hands. Its coating makes it very soft.
• EASY TO USE
• ABILITY TO CUSTOMIZE TIME IN EACH PROGRAM
• HIGH TECH &#38; DESIGN: Duo Pro is a handheld stimulator with modern and innovative design, compact size, backlit display.
• A FULL COMPLEMENT OF THE BEST PROGRAMS: To provide superior performance with ease of use.
• SPORTS AND PERFORMANCE: 7 essential programs for training and sports performance.
• FITNESS: 20 programs to achieve and maintain a perfect physical shape. The best solution to restore the balance and beauty of your body.
• HEALTH AND WELLBEING: 8 specific applications for the treatment of pain, acute and chronic inflammatory disorders in the musculoskeletal system.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Duo-Pro.jpg'></p><p>SPECIFICATIONS<br />
Channels: 2 independent channels<br />
Frequency: 1 to 120 Hz<br />
Power: 40 mA per channel<br />
Pulse width: 50 to 320 μs<br />
Waveform: square, biphasic, symmetrical<br />
and balanced wave<br />
Power supply: 3 batteries 1,5 V AAA<br />
Device Class II Type BF</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 bag<br />
A stimulator PRO DUO<br />
2 cables for connecting the electrodes<br />
4 Square self-adhesive electrodes<br />
4 Rectangular self-adhesive electrodes<br />
1 Operating Manual<br />
3 AAA Batteries</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DUO TENS</title>
		<link>/product/duo-tens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:08:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1133</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[4 Fitness, Beauty, Wellness – 16 Pain –Tens
Globus presents the new Duo Tens electrostimulator with a completely innovated design and performance.
PROGRAMMABLE: Duo Tens has 6 free memories where it is possible to insert the desired parameters and to create your personalized
programs.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.
PAIN: It eliminates the pain with the special pulses of the TENS currents that, stimulating your body in a soft way, enables you to recover your
health, wellness and a renovated life enjoyment.
FITNESS, BEAUTY &#38; WELNESS: body beauty is the expression of a wellness state and a form balance that you have to value and defend from the attacks of time and sedentary life. With Duo Tens you can care for your body, defending its vitality and beauty using the main programs for physical shape.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/DuoTens.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 2 independent<br />
CHANNELS Frequency: 0 –<br />
150 Hz<br />
Power: 100 mA per channel Pulse<br />
amplitude: 50 – 400 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical and compensated wave<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Backlit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS Duo Tens Stimulator<br />
2 Cables for electrode connection<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular<br />
electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ELITE SII</title>
		<link>/product/elite-sii/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1135</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[30 Sport - 44 Fitness, Beauty, Wellness – 16 Pain –Tens
6 Prevention – 3 Rehabilitation - 1 Incontinence
Globus presents the new Elite SII electrostimulator with a completely improved design and performance.

PROGRAMMABLE: ELITE SII has 6 free memories where it is possible to insert the desired parameters and to create your personalized programs.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.
PREVENTION: 6 programs to reinforce main articulations and to prevent traumas and injuries.
SPORT: EliteSII is programed to selectively stimulate fast and slow fibers in order to train different muscle qualities
FITNESS, BEAUTY &#38; WELNESS: Thanks to its compactness, lightness and power supply with rechargeable battery, Elite SII is the ideal tool to make an home exercise program to reach and maintain the physical shape.
You can care for your body and defend its vitality and beauty with the electrostimulation beauty treatments.
REHABILITATION &#38; PAIN
REHABILITATION: Muscle stimulation programs are particularly indicated for functional recovery after surgical articulation interventions and after immobilization time
PAIN: It eliminates the pain with the special pulses of the TENS currents that, stimulating your body in a soft way, enables you to recover your health, wellness and a renovated life enjoyment.
INCONTINENCE: one specific program to treat at home this common disorder.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Elite-S2.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 2 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0 –150 Hz<br />
Power: 100 mA p.p. for channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 50 – 400 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic, symmetrical<br />
and compensated wave<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Back-lit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS ELITE SII Stimulator<br />
1 Cables for electrode connection<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FIT &#038; BEAUTY</title>
		<link>/product/fit-beauty/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1137</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[13 G-Pulse Face-Skin © - 65 Beauty – 58 Fitness – 22 Sport –12
Tens-Pain – 3 Rehabilitation – 3 Incontinence – 12 Microcurrents
–
FACE-SKIN TREATMENTS: Fit &#38; Beauty presents the new innovative and regenerative G-PULSE currents, proposed for Aesthetic and
Beauty applications and able to regenerate the collagen production in the tissues.
G-TRODE HANDPIECE Fit &#38; Beauty is equipped with a special handpiece that permits, using the G-PULSE programs, to obtain a more effective skin stimulation.
NEW TRENDY CARRIAGE CASE: Fit &#38; Beauty is supplied with a practical modern carrying case in aluminum and eco leather that can be carried in an easy way and that makes you feel always fashionable.
FACE &#38; BREAST AREAS: Fit &#38; Beauty is equipped with a complete set of programs for face and breast toning
MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 10 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.
PROGRAMMABLE: 10 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity regulation.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button .
RUN TIME FUNCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 15 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/FitBeauty.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz &#8211; Power: 120 mA<br />
per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical, compensated wave<br />
Power supply: mains or battery<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 Fit &amp; Beauty stimulator<br />
1 G-Trode handpiece<br />
4 electrostimulation cables and 2<br />
microcurrent cables<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes and 4<br />
self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Gel bottle<br />
1 power supply<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GENESY 1200 Pro</title>
		<link>/product/genesy-1200-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1144</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[• MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position images directly on the display.
• RUN TIME: it permits to modify the contraction parameters during the stimulation.
• FAST MENU: for a more rapid navigation
• GRAPHIC LCD DISPLAY
• FUNCTIONAL RE-EDUCATION: the programs are designed to carry out a proper rehabilitation of the injured person through specific programs with square wave, denervated and interferential.
• MICROCURRENTS (MENS): Genesy 1200 offers the new and innovative "regenerative" and "therapeutic" currents, proposed for Sport, Beauty and, especially, Health treatments.
• PROGRAMMABLE: 15 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
• 2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
• MULTI-USER: Genesy 1200 permits to share the stimulator among 25 users, keeping the setting and the preferences unchanged.
• AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): Genesy 1200 is the only stimulator that permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity regulation.
• MEMO MODE: Genesy 1200 permits to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.
• SYNCROSTIM: it is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button .
• LAST 10: Genesy 1200 stored the last executed programs. Therefore, they are available for a rapid and easy execution.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Genesy-300_English-Display.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Square, biphasic, symmetrical,<br />
compensated wave<br />
Power supply: mains or battery<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS GENESY 1200 Stimulator<br />
4 Cables for electrode connection<br />
2 Cables for microcurrents and<br />
ionophoresis<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GENESY 300 PRO</title>
		<link>/product/genesy-300-pro/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1140</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 3 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.
AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity regulation.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button.
RUN TIME FUNCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment
PROGRAMMABLE: 5 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 15 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Genesy-300_English-Display.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical and compensated wave<br />
Power supply: rechargeable battery<br />
Back-lit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS GENESY 300 Pro Stimulator<br />
4 Cables for electrode connection<br />
2 Cables for microcurrents and<br />
ionophoresis<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GENESY 3000</title>
		<link>/product/genesy-3000/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1148</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[”EASY PROGRAM” ELECTROTHERAPY MENU: a section where it is possible to rapidly set a program setting the desired parameters (time, frequency, body area) and to execute specific treatments using EMS and Russian(Kotz) currents.
MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 25 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.
AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity regulation.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button .
RUN TIME FUNCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment
PROGRAMMABLE: 15 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 30 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Genesy3000_EnglishDisplay.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz &#8211; Power: 120<br />
mA per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Square, biphasic, symmetrical,<br />
compensated wave<br />
Power supply: by the mains or with<br />
battery<br />
Backlit display<br />
Device in II A class<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carriage bag<br />
1 GLOBUS GENESY 3000 Stimulator<br />
4 Cables for electrode connection<br />
2 Cables for microcurrents and<br />
ionophoresis<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
2 iono electrodes + 2 Elastic Band<br />
1 power supply unit<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>GENESY 3000 Rehab</title>
		<link>/product/genesy-3000-rehab/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siaru1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 03:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=product&#038;p=1146</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[”EASY PROGRAM” ELECTROTHERAPY MENU: a section where it is possible to rapidly set a program by setting the desired parameters (time, frequency, body area) and to execute specific treatments using EMS and Russian (Kotz) currents.
MULTI-USER: it permits to store up to 25 different users and to create a library of personalized programs depending on individual aims.
AUTOMATIC MODE (AUTO STIM®): it permits to execute a program in automatic mode with no need of intervening manually in the intensity regulation.
SYNCROSTIM: It is possible to increase the intensity of the 4 channels simultaneously using only one button .
RUN TIME FUNCTION: this function permits to modify the time, the frequency and the pulse amplitude during the treatment
PROGRAMMABLE: 15 free memories, only for EMS and TENS.
2+2 MODE: it permits to execute two different programs simultaneously.
FAVORITES: it permits to store up to 15 programs for each user
LAST 10: it stores the last 10 executed programs
WORKING TIME: It indicates the total usage time of the device
MY TRAINER: it shows the electrode position on the display
STIM LOCK]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><img src='/wp-content/uploads/2017/05/Genesy3000Rehab_EnglishDisplay.jpg'></p><p>TECHNICAL FEATURES<br />
Channels: 4 independent CHANNELS<br />
Frequency: 0,3 – 150 Hz<br />
Power: 120 mA per channel<br />
Pulse amplitude: 40 – 450 μs<br />
Wave form: Square, biphasic,<br />
symmetrical and compensated wave<br />
Power supply: mains or battery<br />
Device in II A class<br />
Backlit display<br />
In compliance with the directive</p>
<p>EQUIPMENT<br />
1 Carrying case<br />
1 GLOBUS GENESY 3000 Rehab Stimulator<br />
4 Cables for electrode connection<br />
2 cables for microcurrent<br />
4 self-adhesive square electrodes<br />
4 self-adhesive rectangular electrodes<br />
1 Charger<br />
1 Operating manual</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
